export default [
    {
        question: 'Which method removes the last element from an array?',
        options: ['pop()', 'push()', 'shift()', 'unshift()', 'splice()'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which method adds a new element to an array (at the end)?',
        options: ['unshift()', 'shift()', 'concat()', 'pop()', 'push()'],
        correct: 4
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which method can be used to add new items to an array?',
        options: ['concat()', 'splice()', 'push()', 'pop()', 'shift()'],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'method creates a new array by merging existing arrays?',
        options: ['shift()', 'unshift()', 'concat()', 'push()', 'pop()'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator assigns a value to a variable?',
        options: ['+=', '-=', '*=', '/=', '='],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator adds a value to a variable?',
        options: ['-=', '*=', '+=', '/=', '%='],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator subtracts a value from a variable?',
        options: ['+=', '*=', '%=', '-=', '/='],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator multiplies a variable?',
        options: ['-=', '%=', '/=', '+=', '*='],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator divides a variable?',
        options: ['+=', '*=', '/=', '%=', '-='],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which assignment operator assigns a remainder to a variable?',
        options: ['-=', '/=', '*=', '+=', '%='],
        correct: 4
    }
]